Guide to the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Issues and Programs, 1966-2010
  - Subseries IV.6: South Africa, 1966-1996
    - ICCR Reports
      - Multinational Business in South Africa (Executive Summary), 1996 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Ingersoll-Rand, 1989-1994 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Institute on Religion and Democracy (IRD) and South Africa, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Inter-religious Consultation on South Africa: Economic Pressure Strategies to End Apartheid, 1986 April 30-May 2 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - International Paper Company (IPC), 1991-1994 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Issue Group, 1994-1996 (3 Folders) (Box 51, Folder 10 to 12)
    - ITT, 1973, 1987-1992 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Japanese Companies / Hitachi--Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Japanese Computer Companies in South Africa, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Johnson & Johnson, 1987-1994 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - J.P. Morgan
      - General
        - 1976-1985 (Box 33, Folder 27)
        - 1991 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Annual General Meeting, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Kennametal, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Kidder, Peabody & Company, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Kimberly-Clark, 1989-1994 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Kodak, 1986-1990 (2 Folders) (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - Letters
      - Church Letters to Banks, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 47)
      - Letters to Seven Major United States Lenders to South Africa: No Loan Conversions, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 48)
      - Letters to South Africa’s Creditor Banks, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 49)
      - Twelve Bank Letters and Dialogs, per South Africa Interest Group (SAIG), 1989 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Levi-Strauss, 1993 (2 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 13 to 14)
    - Loans
      - Bank Loans, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 51)
      - Lending Update for South Africa, by John E. Lind, 1992 February (Box 25, Folder 52)
      - Recent South Africa Bank Statements, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 53)
      - South Africa Loan Conversion--Legal Brief, 1989 August (Box 25, Folder 54)
      - United States Bank Lending to South Africa--General, 1985-1989 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Luncheon Discussion with Thabo Mbeki, 1995 February 28 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Mailings
      - South Africa Campaign Packet, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - ICCR Mailings on South Africa, circa 1985 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust (MHT)
      - Articles, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Background to Campaign, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - Branch Bank Campaign, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - Campaign, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - Central Labor Council (CLC) Resolution, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - Chants and Fliers, circa 1990 (Box 25, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      - Letters to, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 37)
      - Meeting, 1989 April 21 (Box 25, Folder 38)
      - Scripts: South African Political Prisoners Day, 1990 October 11 (Box 25, Folder 39)
      - Sharpeville Day, 1991 March 21 (Box 25, Folder 40)
      - Support Statements, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Maquiladoras - FM and South Africa Council of Churches (SACC), 1993-1996 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Merck, 1991-1993 (2 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 15 to 16)
    - Merrill Lynch, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing, 1987-1994 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Minorco, 1988-1990 (2 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 19 to 20)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation
      - General
        - 1972-1980 (Box 29, Folder 5)
          (#2)
        - 1985-1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
        - 1986-1989 (Box 51, Folder 22)
      - Campaign--Various Articles, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Chemical Workers Industrial Union (CWIU), 1989 (Box 51, Folder 23)
      - Chronology of Chemical Workers Industrial Union (CWIU) Dispute, 1987-1989 (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - Mobil Memo, 1987 December 18 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Mobil’s Withdrawal, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Prayer Service at Mobil Annual Meeting, 1989 May 11 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - SEC Challenge, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Shareholder Meeting (Phoenix), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Monsanto, 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Motor Industry in South Africa, 1969-1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Motor Study in South Africa, circa 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Motorola, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - National Conference in Support of the African National Congress and Other Democratic Forces for a New South Africa, 1992 November 13-15
      - General (2 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 8 to 9)
      - Codes Workshop (Toward A Code of Conduct: Corporate Responsibility in a New South Africa) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - National Council of Churches Policy on Southern Africa, 1970-1976 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - National Key Points Letter--South Africa, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Newmont (Box 15)
      - General Information, 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - General Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Meeting with Company, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - New York City Testimony, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Nickel, Herman--South Africa Ambassador, 1978-1982 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Oil Tankers to South Africa, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      (Report by Shipping Research Bureau, Amsterdam)
    - Pagan International, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - PepsiCo--General
      - 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Pfizer
      - Meetings with Company, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - General, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Polaroid
      - Polaroid “Experiment”, 1971-1975 (2 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 3-3a)
      - Revolutionary Workers Movement, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Withdrawal from South Africa, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Proxy Statements, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Raytheon, 1990-1991 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Reebok
      - General, 1990-1993 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Reebok Project, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Reports and Articles, 1994-1997 (4 Folders) (Box 51, Folder 14 to 17)
    - Research Papers (Originals), 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Resolutions, 1994-1995 (2 Folders) (Box 51, Folder 18 to 19)
    - Rhodesia Oil
      - Mobil Oil and Rhodesia, 1975-1977 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - Standard Oil of California and Rhodesia, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Texaco and Rhodesia, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - RJR Nabisco, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Shell Oil Company
      (Includes Royal Dutch Shell)
      - Boycott
        - General, 1986-1988 (6 Folders) (Box 52, Folder 1)
        - Chronology, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 2)
        - Churches, 1983-1987 (Box 52, Folder 3)
        - Implementation Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Business Reports (Shell), 1985-1988 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Campaign
        - Australia, 1985-1988 (Box 33, Folder 8)
        - Letters to Institutional Shareholders, 1987-1989 (Box 52, Folder 6)
        - No Buy Campaign, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Church Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Neptune: Notre Dame Center for Post-Apartheid Studies, 1986-1988 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Neptune Strategy Correspondence, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Pagan Controversy, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - “The Shell Game,” 1987 October (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - Shell in South Africa, 1976 June (Box 33, Folder 10)
        (Kairos-Osaci Report)
      - Shell Press, 1986-1991 (4 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 6 to 9)
      - Strategies and Meetings, 1987-1991 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - United Methodist Church (UMC) Affidavit, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Victories, 1988-1991 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - What South Africans Say Re: Royal Dutch/Shell, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Tim. Research in South Africa and Articles on South Africa, 1969-1972 (2 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - South Africa--Miscellaneous, 1978-1981 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - South Africa Clippings, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 50)
    - South Africa Community Reinvestment Project--Final Report, 1st Delegation, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - South Africa Disclosures, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - South Africa Interest Group (SAIG)
      - Annual General Meeting (AGM) Evaluation and Action Plan, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - Chair’s Correspondence, 1987 (2 Folders) (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Meetings and Minutes
        - 1988-1990 (2 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 7 to 8)
        - 1991 September 19 (Box 83, Folder 9)
        - 1991 November 14 (Box 83, Folder 10)
        - 1993 September 22 (Box 83, Folder 11)
        - 1993 November 17 (Box 83, Folder 12)
        - 1994 February 9 (2 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 13 to 14)
    - South Africa Legislative Packet, circa 1986 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - South Africa Symposium, 1981 (2 Folders) (Box 30, Folder 1 to 2)
    - South African National Civic Association (SANCO)
      - Moses Mayekiso, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Training Proposal, 1995 October (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Sullivan, Leon
      - General, 1977-1984 (3 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Corporate Responses to Bill Howard Lester on Sullivan Principles, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Summer Strategy Group, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - A Survey of Corporate Responsibility in Ten South African Companies, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Symposium, 1981
      - General (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Transcript (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Texaco
      - General Information, 1985-1993 (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Meetings with Company, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - United Technologies (UTC), 1990-1994 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Warner Lambert, 1989-1994 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Westinghouse, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - (Box 15)
    - Withdrawal Articles, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - W.R. Grace, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Xerox, 1986-1990 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Subseries IV.7. Tobacco, 1985-1999
    - General
      - General, 1996-1999 (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Articles, Etc., 1991-1992 (Box 110, Folder 2)
      - General Background on Tobacco Companies, 1990-1993 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - Items from September Meeting and Tobacco, 1994-1995 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - Reports, 1995-1998 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Advertising
      - Advertising Workshop, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Counter-Advertising Against Tobacco, 1990-1996 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Marketing and Media, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Advocacy Institute, 1991-1994 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Aetna, 1991-1993 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Allstate, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - American Brands, 1990-1994 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - American Cancer Society, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - American General, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - American International, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - American Lung Association
      - Conference Report, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 13)
      - Non-Independence Day, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Anti-Smoking
      - It Can Be Done Book, 1990-1992 (Box 110, Folder 15)
      - Networks and Contacts, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Bordens, Inc., 1991 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Bristol Mysers and Tobacco, Undated (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Camel Controversy (Joe), 1992-1994 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Canada and Its Anti-Tobacco Movements and Strategies, 1990-1993 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Children / Teenagers, 1990-1996 (2 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 14 to 15)
    - Cigarette Advertisements, 1990-1994 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Cigarette Smoking Statistics, 1989-1993 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Clark, Kimberly
      - General, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 20)
      - Press, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Coalition on Smoking OR Health, 1991-1996 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Council for Tobacco Research, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - CVS/Melville, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Decline of Tobacco Industry, 1990-1994 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Divesting from Tobacco Companies, 1990-1994 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Donations by Tobacco Companies, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Eastman Kodak, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - Employment Issues, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - Episcopal Church Tobacco Resolutions, 1989-1993 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Exporting Tobacco, 1988-1990 (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - Gannett, 1991-1994 (Box 110, Folder 29)
    - Great Western, 1993-1994 (Box 110, Folder 30)
    - Health, General Information on Smoking and, 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 31)
    - Health Care Chaplaincy and Tobacco, 1996-1998 (Box 110, Folder 32)
    - H.B. Fuller, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 33)
    - ICCR
      - Index of Files on Tobacco, Undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - ICCR Information, 1990-1994 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - ICCR Brief on Tobacco, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - ICCR Tobacco Project, Fundraising for, 1987-1990 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - ICCR Memos on Tobacco Companies, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - ICCR Tobacco Press Clips, 1990-1994 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - INFACT, 1990-1994 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Insurance Companies
      - Insurance Companies and HMO Tobacco Investments, 1995-1996 (Box 110, Folder 34)
      - Insurance Companies and Tobacco Investing Memo, 1991-1993 (Box 110, Folder 35)
      - Tobacco Companies and Insurance Companies, 1991-1996 (Box 110, Folder 36)
    - Lawsuits, 1990-1994 (Box 110, Folder 37)
    - Legislation, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 38)
    - Liability, 1985-1990 (Box 110, Folder 39)
    - Liggett, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 40)
    - Loews, 1990-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 110, Folder 41)
    - Marlboro, 1992-1995 (Box 110, Folder 42)
    - Minnesota Tobacco Law, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 43)
    - Negotiations, 1995-1996 (Box 110, Folder 44)
    - New Jersey
      - Ruling: Warning on Cigarettes Doesn’t Preempt Claims, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 45)
      - Shares Drop with New Jersey Ruling of Liability, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 46)
    - New York City Opera and Tobacco, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 47)
    - New York Times and Wall Street Journal Articles on Tobacco Companies and Executives, 1994 (2 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 22 to 23)
    - Nicotine Issues and Information, 1987-1994 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Passive Smoking, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - PepsiCo, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 48)
    - Pharmacies, Tobacco and--General, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 49)
    - Philip Morris
      - General Information, 1989-1994 (Box 110, Folder 50)
      - Annual General Meetings (AGMs), 1990-1992 (Box 110, Folder 51)
      - Bill of Rights Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 110, Folder 52)
      - Counter Advertising, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 53)
      - Mother Beer, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 54)
    - Politics, Tobacco and, 1992-1994 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Press, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Proxies, Tobacco Company, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Resolutions, 1989-1994 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Rite Aid, 1991-1992 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - RJR Nabisco, 1990-1998 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Sales and the Tobacco Industry, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Selling Abroad, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Stanford Response to Tobacco Investment Investigation, 1992 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Stockholders--Top Stockholders, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Surgeon General, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Taxes, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association College Retirement & Equities Fund (TIAA-CREF)
      - General, 1991-1993 (Box 99, Folder 19)
      - Response to Tobacco Investing, 1992 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - Thailand / Trade Laws--Letters to Bush and Hills and Response, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - Third World, Tobacco in the, 1986-1997 (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - Time Warner, 1993-1995 (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - Tobacco Advertising Articles, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 24)
    - Tobacco Free Investing, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 25)
    - Travelers, 1990-1991 (Box 99, Folder 26)
    - United States Tobacco (UST), 1991-1996 (2 Folders) (Box 99, Folder 27 to 28)
    - University and Tobacco Stock, 1990-1991 (Box 99, Folder 29)
    - Unocal, 1994-1996 (Box 99, Folder 30)
    - Walgreens, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 31)
    - Women and Smoking, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - World Health Organization (WHO), 1991-1992 (Box 99, Folder 32)
- Series V: Company Files, 1966-2009
  The ICCR kept general files on many corporations. The files include company materials and records documenting to ICCR’s activities that are related to specific companies.
  The company materials include shareholder information such as annual reports, information on annual shareholder meetings, brochures, and company materials on issues of interest to the ICCR.
  These files also include resolutions (with cover letters) submitted to the company by ICCR member organizations. Larger files may also include communication with the company on requests for information, clippings, and communications with entities such as the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
  Additional records related to specific companies may also be found in the records related to Issues and Programs (Series IV) and in the SEC Files (Series VI).
  - 3M, 1976-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 1 to 2)
  - A & P, 1977-1978 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Abbott Laboratories, 1974-1998 (4 Folders) (Box 107, Folder 2 to 5)
  - AES, 1995-2000 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Aetna, 1987-2000 (2 Folders) (Box 107, Folder 7 to 8)
  - Air Express International, 1996-1997 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Albany International, 1996-1997 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Albertson’s Inc., 1992-1999 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Alcoa, 1974-2000 (2 Folders) (Box 107, Folder 12 to 13)
  - Allegheny Power, 1979-2001 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Allergan, 1990-2000 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Allstate, 1995-1999 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - AMAX Inc., 1970-1981 (2 Folders) (Box 107, Folder 17 to 18)
  - American Cyanide, 1976-1992 (2 Folders) (Box 107, Folder 19 to 20)
  - American Electric Power (AEP), 1973-1999 (7 Folders) (Box 87, Folder 1 to 7)
  - American Express, 1979-2000 (4 Folders) (Box 87, Folder 8 to 11)
  - American General, 1993-1999 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - American International Group (AIG), 1986-1998 (2 Folders) (Box 87, Folder 13 to 14)
  - American Telephone & Telegraph (AT&T), 1980-1991 (6 Folders) (Box 87, Folder 15 to 20)
  - American Telephone & Telegraph (AT&T), 1979-1999 (6 Folders) (Box 88, Folder 1 to 6)
  - AMP, 1993-1996 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - AMR, 1986-1996 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Anheuser Busch, 1966, 1978-1979, 1993-1997 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - A.O. Smith, 1992-1998 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Apache, 1993-1996 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Archer-Daniels-Midlands, 1993-1996 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Arthur D. Little, 1969-1971, Undated (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Avery Dennison, 1987-1991 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Avon, 1971-1990 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Baker Hughes, 1986-2001 (2 Folders) (Box 88, Folder 14 to 15)
  - Ball Corporation, 1989-2000 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Bandag, 1977, 1987-1998 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Bank of America, 1971-1999 (6 Folders) (Box 93, Folder 2 to 7)
  - Bank of Boston, 1977-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 93, Folder 8 to 9)
  - Bank One, 1991-1997 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Bankers Trust, 1992-1998 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Barnett Banks, 1987-1997 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Bausch & Lomb, 1987-1995 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Baxter International, 1981-1999 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - BB & T, 1998-1999 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - BDM International, 1985-1987 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - B/E Aerospace, 1996-1999 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Beatrice, 1972-1985 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Becton Dickinson, 1980-1996 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Bed, Bath & Beyond, 1997-2009 (3 Folders) (Box 93, Folder 20 to 22)
  - Bechtel, 1973-1979 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Bell Atlantic, 1985-2000 (2 Folders) (Box 94, Folder 2 to 3)
  - Best Buy, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Bestfoods, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Bethlehem Steel, 1973-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 94, Folder 6 to 7)
  - Boatmen’s, 1978-1994 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Boeing, 1971-2002 (6 Folders) (Box 94, Folder 9 to 14)
  - Boise Cascade, 1990-1997 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Borden, 1975-1996 (2 Folders) (Box 94, Folder 16 to 17)
  - Borg-Warner, 1978-1986 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Boston Edison, 1978-1983, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - BP
    - 1975-1999, (7 Folders) (Box 7, Folder 1 to 7)
    - 1993-1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Brascan, circa 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Bristol Myers, 1975-1999, (9 Folders) (Box 7, Folder 8 to 16)
  - Brooklyn Union Gas, 1987-1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Browning Ferris, 1984-1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Burlington Industries, 1976-1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Burlington Northern, 1972-1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Burlington Northern Santa Fe (BNSF), 1984-1986, (2 Folders) (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Cabot, 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Campbell Soup, 1976-1995, (2 Folders) (Box 8, Folder 6 to 7)
  - Carnation, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Carolina Power, 1985-1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Caterpillar, 1970-2000, (4 Folders) (Box 8, Folder 10 to 13)
  - CBI Industries, 1988-1994 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - CBS, 1970-1999, (2 Folders) (Box 7, Folder 21 to 22)
  - Cendant, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Champion International, 1989-1997 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Chase, 1971-1999, (5 Folders) (Box 8, Folder 16 to 20)
  - Chevron, 1973-1998 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Chris Craft, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Chrysler, 1977-1997, (3 Folders) (Box 10, Folder 4 to 6)
  - Chubb Corporation, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Church & Dwight, 1991-1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Church’s Fried Chicken, 1985-1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Ciba-Geigy, 1986-1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Cigna, 1973-2000, (2 Folders) (Box 10, Folder 11 to 12)
  - Cincinnati Gas, 1982-1984, (2 Folders) (Box 10, Folder 13 to 14)
  - Circuit City, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cisco, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Citigroup/Citicorp, 1976-2000, (9 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 3 to 11)
  - Clear Channel, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Clorox, 1991-1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Coca-Cola, 1976-2001, (6 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 14 to 19)
  - Colgate, 1980-1997, (3 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Colt, 1977-1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Columbia HCA, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth Edison, 1977-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 20 to 21)
  - Computer Science (CSC), 1986 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Con Agra, 1978-2000 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Con Edison
    - 1977-1984, (4 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 1 to 4)
    - 1980-1983, (2 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 24 to 25)
  - Conn Gen, 1978-1999 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Cook Industries, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Conseco, 1991-2001 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Consolidated Paper, 1990-1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Constal Corporation, 1991-1999, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 9 to 10)
  - Constellation Energy, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Control Data, 1977-1989, (3 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 12 to 14)
  - Cooper Industries, 1989-2000, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 15 to 16)
  - Corning, 1990-1996 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Corwin Castle, 1989, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - CPC, 1972-1997 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Cracker Barrel, 1991-1996 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Crocker National, 1976-1985, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 21 to 22)
  - Crown Cork & Seal, 1987-1997 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - CSX, 1994-2001, (2 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Cummins Engine, 1977-1997 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - CVS, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Cypress, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Dana, 1989-2000 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Dart & Kraft, 1981-1986 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Dayton Power, 1978-1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Deere & Company, 1975-1998, (2 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 9 to 10)
  - Delmonte, 1975-1980, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 11 to 12)
  - Delta, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Detroit Edison, 1979-1995 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Dial, 1983-1996 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Diamond Shamrock, 1983-1991 (Box 17, Folder 16)